<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quest Manager</string>

    <!-- Following block of strings is the level text for the dungeon screen-->
    <string name="introduction_text">In this dungeon you will face many dangerous foes. You will need to use your Power and skills to make it through. While the danger is real and constant, there is also great treasure to be earned for those brave enough to seek it. Shall you continue adventurer?</string>
    <string name="level_end">With the battle over, you press on, further into the dungeon…</string>

    <string name="level_1">You go further into the decrepit dungeon. The smell of mildew permeates the torch-lit corridors, and you hear a soft squelch as you move across the moss-covered ground. You begin to almost become calm as you round a corner and see glowing red eyes in the darkness. You ready your weapon and prepare for the encounter.</string>
    <string name="level_2">The sound of your feet sloshing through water echoes on the walls of the cavern. It starts out ankle-deep, then becomes knee-deep. Bright blue flickering lights dance around you. As you’re distracted by them, something rises from the water!</string>
    <string name="level_3">Flames flicker off the walls ahead. Your face reddens and dampens with sweat. You keep glancing down at the obsidian beneath you, watching for cracks where glowing, pulsating magma seeps through. When you next look up, you see a monster emerge from the flames!</string>
    <string name="level_4">Your body shivers, more and more with each step you take. Ice coats the floor and walls. You catch your own reflection in a frozen wall… and the reflection of a monster sneaking up behind you! You whip around and draw your weapon.</string>
    <string name="level_5">This room is filled with stalagmites and stalactites, enough to almost turn it into a maze. The only sound is the consistent dripping of water. At one point, you have to suck in your stomach to squeeze through a pair of pillars… and on the other side, you’re met with a monster!</string>
    <string name="level_6">There’s no light in this cave. No cracks in the ceiling, no sparkling crystals in the walls, no magical glowing bugs. Just you and your torch. And then, the light of a giant pair of eyes. You throw the torch at the creature’s feet, revealing its full form.</string>
    <string name="level_7">The first thing you notice upon entering this room is the smell, a strange mix of wet fur and.. Cheese? Milk gone bad? It is not a pleasant smell. And it’s not long before you stumble across the monster responsible for it.</string>
    <string name="level_8">Not far down the tunnel, you begin hearing a concerning sound. At first it just sounds like nails on a chalkboard, but as you approach its source, it sounds more like metal scratching against stone. You do your best to sneak up on the creature responsible for the racket, but before you can land a sneak attack, it whips around to face you.</string>
    <string name="level_9">A strained howling echoes from further down, bouncing off the walls. At first it sounds kind of lonely, to the extent you almost want to call out in response. But the closer you get, the deeper and more ferocious it becomes, until you finally see the creature responsible.</string>

    <string name="level_boss">This room is smaller than the others you’ve ventured through, and eerily quiet. Even stranger, there’s a robed figure standing in the center. You step forward, weapon drawn, knowing it must be the dreaded Master Martin. He adjusts his glasses with a smirk and pulls out his Tome of Judgment. It’s boss time!</string>
    <string name="boss_end">Martin falls to the ground, his power depleted. “You have grown, adventurer. But there is always more to learn.” With that, he casts a final spell, surrounding himself with smoke. You charge through it, but when it clears, he has disappeared, deeper into the dungeon. At least you can claim all the gold he left behind.</string>

    <!--Following block of strings are the section headings for the help screen-->
    <string name="qGeneral">General Information</string>
    <string name="qHome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="qQuest">Quest Screen</string>
    <string name="qProfile">Profile Screen</string>
    <string name="qShop">Shop Screen</string>
    <string name="qDungeon">Dungeon Screen</string>
    <string name="qCredits">Credits</string>

    <!--And this is all the explanatory text for the help screen.-->
    <string name="aGeneral"><![CDATA[
    <p>Thank you for downloading Quest Manager!</p>
    <p>Your goal, hero, is simple: complete enough <b>Quests</b>
    to both raise your <b>Productivity Level</b> high enough
    that you can conquer the <b>Dungeon of Responsibilities</b>,
    and simultaneously, thanks to the prior motivation,
    become better at completing your tasks in the real world!</p>
    <p>Below you will find explanations of how each of the screens of this app functions.</p>
    <p>We wish you luck, hero!</p>]]></string>

    <string name="aHome"><![CDATA[
    <p>The home screen can be thought of as your adventuring hub.</p>
    <p>At the top you will see your current <b>Main Quest</b> (set on the <b>Quest screen</b>).</p>
    <p>Next to your character image is your <b>Name</b>
    (as entered when you first made your character; it unfortunately cannot be changed)
    and your currently set Title.
    <b>Titles</b> are earned as <b>achievements</b> for completing specific tasks or a certain number of tasks
    (see the <b>Profile Screen</b> section of this page).</p>
    <p>Below that is your Level, Power, and EXP (experience points).
    <b>Power</b> and <b>EXP</b> are both increased by completing <b>Quests</b>.
    Earning enough EXP ups your <b>Level</b>. It represents how much your productivity has increased!</p>
    <p>Power is used to enter the <b>Dungeon</b>.
    To do well in the Dungeon, you will want to increase your stats.
    This is done by leveling up (see the <b>Profile Screen</b>),
    and by buying weapons with the money you earn from the Dungeon at the <b>Shop</b>.</p>
    <p>At the bottom are buttons to take you the Quest, Profile, Shop, and Dungeon screens,
    which each have their own sections on this page if you have questions about them.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="aQuest"><![CDATA[
    <p>The Quest Screen is where you make and view <b>Quests</b>; aka, the tasks you have to complete.
    It is divided into three sections: Current Quests, Daily Quests, and Completed Quests.</p>
    <p>The <b>Current Quests</b> tab lets you see the tasks you have signed up for and have yet to complete.
    Every one of these Quests has a Name, Description, Due Date, Due Time, and Difficulty (from 1 to 5).
    You can make a new Quest by pressing the <b>New Quest</b> button at the bottom of this screen.</p>
    <p>If you click on a Quest in the list,
    you can edit it, delete it, move its position, or mark it as complete.
    A newly created quest can not be completed for <b>1 hour</b> after creation.
    The Quest you have at the top of your list will be set as your <b>Main Quest</b>
    and appear at the top of the Home Screen.
    Completing a Quest will earn you EXP (amount depending on its Difficulty)
    and move it to the <b>Completed Quests</b> tab, where you can view everything you have accomplished :)</p>
    <p><b>Daily Tasks</b> are chores that are auto-generated and refresh every day.
    They are reminders to do things like eat, drink water,
    take care of your personal hygiene, get some rest, and socialize.
    You can add some of your own as well with the New Daily Quest button.
    They are a smaller but reliable source of EXP and Power, and they are important to do,
    so be sure to do them and check them off the list!</p>]]></string>

    <string name="aProfile"><![CDATA[
    <p>The <b>Profile Screen</b> is where you can view your player stats and achievements.</p>
    <p>You can increase your stats here via the + buttons if you have <b>Skill Points</b> to spend.
    You earn Skill Points from leveling up via the EXP you get from finishing <b>Quests</b>.
    Your stats determine your performance in the <b>Dungeon</b>, so assign your points wisely!</p>
    <p><i>One line description of the affect of each stat here.</i></p>
    <p><b>Achievements</b> are earned from completing specific tasks, or a certain number of tasks.
    Each achievement gets you a <b>Title</b>
    that you can set here to appear alongside your name on the <b>Home Screen</b>.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="aShop"><![CDATA[
    <p>The <b>Shop Screen</b> is where you spend the money you earn in the <b>Dungeon</b>.</p>
    <p>The weapons you buy here, in addition to being cosmetic upgrades,
    give a boost to your stats, which are viewable on the <b>Profile Screen</b>.
    The newest weapon you buy will be automatically equipped,
    but you can manually switch back to another one by tapping it and pressing the Equip button.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="aDungeon"><![CDATA[
    <p>The <b>Dungeon of Responsibilities</b> is where you put your <b>Power</b> to use.
    If you choose to Continue, you will encounter a monster!</p>
    <p>The monster will attack you (or at least try to) on its turn, lowering your Power.
    Do not let your Power get to <b>0</b>, or you will lose some of your money as you flee!</p>
    <p>On your turn, you can either attack the monster, defend to block and reflect damage,
    power yourself up to make your next attack hit harder,
    or retreat to save your Power and try again next time.</p>
    <p>Defeating a monster will earn you money that can be spent on the <b>Shop Screen</b>,
    and will allow you to progress deeper into the dungeon.</p>
    <p>Every time you flee or are kicked out of the dungeon,
    you will have to start back at level 1 when you re-enter.</p>
    <p>There may be someone extra powerful waiting for you a ways down…</p>]]></string>

    <string name="aCredits"><![CDATA[
    <p>"Quest Manager" application created by
    Alexis Francis, Jenna Denomme, John Proctor, Alex Roberts, and Jeffrey Stewart.</p>
    <p>Art by Alexis Francis.</p>
    <p>Copyright Wheaton College Fall 2021</p>]]></string>

</resources>